[{"answer": "Two years. Nearly two years of my life...looking for the remains of that Monkey...a piece of his legendary Golden Hooped Rod...or some sign of the that place.  Nine men perished on the journey. Rest of us nearly died from starvation or one of the many horrible deseases we discovered...  We still came back empty handed", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Give up?!?... my friend, we spent thirteen months in that place!...another seven in that place!..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " One mustn't give up so easily, that place", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "But none in that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Give up?!?... my friend, we spent thirteen months in that place!...another seven in that place!..", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " There was no proof...archeological or anthropological...to indicate that my friend ever visited that place..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Means nothing. The rivers of that place have been plagued by various that place and Scavengers since the 16th Century.  Not much evidence, my friend", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " my friend, there are countless undiscovered African tribes...all with various obscure beliefs and practices...  One tribe may wear peach stones... another may wear banana peels..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah...well you're gettin' on my nerves, Miss... Miss..", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " my friend..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Who's my friend", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "that place?... He journeyed to that place?..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "The Zarnbesi River! It has a reputation for its deadly water snakes..", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " It will also be our logical path", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " In all my years of anthropology... I've never run across anyone or anything quite like Scraggy", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You're looking very lecherous", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Your pathetic lives will be spared. For now.  But everything we find in the Lost City...belongs to ME", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " It is my way. Or you've got no head", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I don't have money..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "She is a wonderful treasure... Eh?..", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I have no deals with dead men", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why?..", "docId": "Indiana-Jones-IV.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " So am I", "qsentId": 24}]